So, I'm prepping all the the gear that I
will need for the race. We have been
developing
this shoe with normal.
We call it the NN 202. It's the the
pattern pending. Very excited to run
with those.
And we've been developing this vest that
it's kind of a t-shirt and a vest. A
cooling one so I can put some ice and
have all the hydration I need for the
for the race. With that, I will wear a
cap that I have modified a bit to to
keep a bit more the the moisture and the
the cold. Thinking about keeping the
the lungs where we run public so we are
able to preserve them and to access them
for for long. Sunglasses are from from
Julbo. Very light. I will
have a
two pairs like to change sometimes if
in any stations to go a bit faster. And
then to record all the data during the
race and to see a bit my pace. I will be
using the the Apex the Coros Apex and
the heart rate monitor. And then for
nutrition, now we are preparing all the
the mixes with issues the first hours I
will be using more of a mix of fats and
and carbs. And then like
going further on like I will be using
more carbs. The gel mix on the
on the last hours where it's mostly like
a carbohydrate. So, that's basically the
gear that I will have during the race.